约翰休斯作品
片名：红粉佳人
老爸 7点半了!
Daddy, it's 7.30!
爸 起床了!
Daddy, wake up!
早啊 爸爸 快起床
Morning, Daddy. Come on, wake up!
快点起床
Wake up! Come on, wake up.
- 这是你的咖啡 - 我在哪儿?
- There's your coffee right there. - Where am I?
把这个喝了
Here, I want you to drink this.
接着洗洗澡穿好衣服 你的衣服在这
Then take a shower and get dressed. Your clothes are there.
之后去找那女人面试 你答应过今天去的
Then I want you to see the woman about the job. Today. You promised.
我知道 要不是你在我耳边嗦 我能做点什么?
I know. What would I do without you nagging me all the time?
你真的想让我回答?
You really want me to answer that?
我最近回来的晚 我们没多少机会聊天
Yeah, I've been gettin' in kinda late lately. We haven't had a chance to talk.
别担心 也没多少可说的
Don't worry about it. There hasn't been a lot to say.
- 你好吧 - 没事
- Is everything all right with you? - Yeah.
- 学校还好吧 - 不好 一直就这样呗
- Is school good? - No, but it never is.
- 有人邀请你去毕业舞会吗? - 还没有
- Have you been asked to the prom? - No. Not yet.
上次我说你美呆了是什么时候
When was the last time I told you how beautiful you are?
昨天吧
About yesterday.
- 转过去 - 干嘛
- Turn around. - What?
让我看看你的美衫
You know what. Let me see this outfit.
- 这是你最新的创作? - 就是它了
- Is this your latest creation? - This is it.